idclips.com 2016-06-08

# Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.OnlineRiver.com and Online River, LLC and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Online River, LLC include www.OnlineRiver.com and Online River. The Online River website is a Ecommerce site and a Superstore for Security, Identification and Point of Sale where information is given regarding products for purchase online or through other communication. site. By using the Online River website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

Online River may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase Online River's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Online River. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Online River website.

Online River encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Online River so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Online River is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Online River website.

**Use of your Personal Information**

Online River collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Online River may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Online River and its affiliates. Online River may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Online River does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Online River may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Online River, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Online River will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Online River or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Online River; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Online River, or the public.

**Security of your Personal Information**

Online River secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Children Under Thirteen**

Online River does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Online River by clicking an Unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email communication from us.  We will delete your email address from our list of customers and contacts such you request it by emailing [info@onlineriver.com](mailto:info@onlineriver.com).

**Changes to this Statement**

Online River will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Online River encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Online River is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

Online River welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Online River has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Online River at:

Online River, LLC

606 Post Road East, STE 723

Westport, Connecticut 06880

Email Address:

info@onlineriver.com

Telephone number:

203-801-5900

Effective as of May 15, 2015
